hungryhouse.co.uk 2014-06-25

# Takeaway Food Delivery

  1. Introduction

Last updated 27 February, 2009.

We are dedicated to protecting the privacy of people using this website. We take the confidentiality of personal data seriously. By accessing and using this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the processing of your data as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy only relates to personal data collected by hungryhouse.com Ltd. through this webste. It does not cover personal data provided to hungryhouse.com Ltd. by any other means or via any other website.

| hungryhouse.com Ltd. complies with the principles of the 'Data Protection Act, 1998' and is registered with the Information Commissioner's Office who oversee this act.  
---|---  
  
  2. Personal Information

We only collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information provided will only be used for the purposes outlined at the time of collection.

You can access the Welcome page and browse our site without disclosing your personal information.

Orders

Personal information required during the order process includes name, address, phone number, email address and other similar information used to identify you and complete an order.

Personal information collected at our site will be shared with a restaurant when processing your order. We have an agreement with all member restaurants, restricting disclosure or further processing of personal information provided to them by us.

Your personal information will be used to notify you of your order status.

Personal information will not be shared with any of our business partners or affiliates without your permission. It is treated as confidential, and will not be disclosed to outside parties, unless compelled by applicable legislation.

We only send marketing emails and/or SMS to those people who have specifically requested to receive this information.

Introductions

When a member introduces a friend, we store the friend's email address so the member can track the status of their introductions. This also allows reminders to be sent if necessary. The person receiving the introduction can remove their email address from our system at any time via a link in the introduction email, or by sending an email directly to us at [help@hungryhouse.com](mailto:%20help@hungryhouse.com).

  3. Verifying, updating and amending personal information

Members

Should your personal information change, you can correct or update this information instantly by editing your member profile at any time.

When editing your member profile or submitting an order, we only ever reveal the last 5 digits of any saved credit card numbers.

To remove your personal information and cancel your membership, send an email from your registered email address to [help@hungryhouse.com](mailto:%20help@hungryhouse.com). Your membership and personal details will be removed within 5 days.

Guests

Users who order as guests cannot view or change their details on the website once an order has been submitted. Any changes which affect the fulfilment of an order should be communicated directly to the applicable restaurant.

  4. Cookies

When you visit our site, our server sends your computer a "cookie." This cookie is a small packet of information that identifies you as a user of our system. Cookies save you time by retaining your contact information. Cookies do not deliver viruses, and can only be read by the server that sent you the cookie.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. Please bear in mind however, that you may not be able to use all the features of our site if cookies are disabled.

We may use third-party cookies as part of remarketing activities we conduct with Google and/or other third-party vendors, to help provide you with relevant promotional offers as you use the Internet. As part of these remarketing activities, these third-party cookies may record your visits to this Web site and Web sites visited prior to using this Web site.

Such cookies can then be used to serve advertisements to you on other Web sites. You may choose to be exempt from the use of Google remarketing cookies at the [Google advertising privacy page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). Alternatively, you may opt-out of remarketing on the Google network and similar networks at the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Opting out will not prevent advertisements from being served to you on the Internet; it will only affect advertisements that utilize remarketing cookies to serve advertisements on the specified advertising networks. We are not responsible for the activities of other parties that may not comply with your opt-out requests.

  5. Security

hungryhouse.com Ltd. holds personal data in accordance with UK data protection legislation.

The technology that we use and the policies that we have implemented are intended to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use.

Where appropriate, we attempt to provide for the secure transmission of information, such as credit card details, from your computer to our server by utilising SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption software. However, due to the inherent open nature of the internet, we cannot guarantee that all data transmitted will be secure. Use of this website demonstrates your assumption of this risk.

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information please [contact us](http://hungryhouse.co.uk/contact).

  6. Links to Third Party Websites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the personal data collected on this website and does not apply to third party websites you may access from here. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites and we advise customers to read the privacy policies of other websites before registering any personal data.

  7. Minors

No information may be submitted to this website by persons under the age of 18 without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, nor may persons under the age of 18 make purchases or other legal acts on this site without such consent, unless permitted by applicable legislation.

  8. Third Party Advertising

We may use a third party to serve advertisements on our site. Cookies may be associated with these advertisements to enable the advertiser to track the number of anonymous users responding to the campaign. We do not access or control cookies placed by third parties.

  9. Changes

This Privacy Policy may change at our discretion at any time, and without notice. It is your responsiblity to periodically review this page for updates which shall come into effect once posted. The date at the top of this document indicates when the last change was made.

  10. Contact

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted by email at [help@hungryhouse.com](mailto:%20help@hungryhouse.com)
